[Music]
The best feeling in the world is when
you take a step in the right
direction towards achieving the goals
you aspire
for, moving to a bigger
home or helping your kids achieve their
dream
careers or fulfilling your parents'
longdue wishes. But as you pursue these
bigger goals, let's also cherish smaller
personal moments too. Plan that dream
vacation, upgrade your car for that road
trip. And for every such big and small
moment of happiness, you need one plan
that gives you both. A bit for the
future and a bit for the present.
Presenting ICICI Pro Gold. A plan that
gives you immediate income with the
choice of receiving income instantly
within 7 days of policy issuance from
the first month or first year for a
minimum of 30 years and with the
flexibility to extend the policy term
until the age of 99 years along with
lumpsum on maturity. Life cover
throughout the policy term. Flexibility
of accumulation or withdrawal of income
any time. Guaranteed boosters every 5
years. Choice to defer income and
receive higher income
later. ICIC Pro Gold offers you the
choice of three plan options. Immediate
income, immediate income with booster,
deferred income. The choice is yours.
Let's say a 35year-old male invests one
lakh every year for 10 years and opts
for lifelong income. Then his policy
will mature at the age of 99 years. In
case he chooses immediate income plan
option, he will get an annual income of
Rs.
37,000 starting from the end of first
year till the age of 99 years and
lumpsum amount of Rs 1.66 cr when the
policy matures at the age of 99 years at
an ARR of 8%.
[Music]
And if he chooses immediate income with
booster plan option, he will get a
guaranteed booster payout of 12,500
rupees every fifth year along with an
annual income of 36,000 rupees starting
from the end of first year till the age
of 99 years and lumsum amount of 1.47 cr
at maturity at an ARR of 8%.
If he wants to save for the future, he
can go for the deferred income option.
For example, today at the age of 35, if
he defers the income by 11 years, he
will get a higher annual income of 1.03
lakh from the age of 47 till the age of
99 years and maturity benefit of
76.07 lakhs at the age of 99 years at an
AR of 8%.
Not only this, in each of these plan
options, he will also receive a life
cover for the entire policy term. The
policy also offers the flexibility to
offset premiums by accumulating income
in the savings wallet. One plan that
understands your today's and tomorrow's
needs and gives you a bit for the future
and a bit for the present. With ICICI
Pro Gold, ensure that your tomorrow
starts today.
[Music]